<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Education on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/education/</link><description>Recent content in Education on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:42:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Education Initiatives for Adoption — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-21)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-21-education-initiatives-for-adoption/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:42:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-21-education-initiatives-for-adoption/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="education-initiatives-for-adoption-empowering-the-knowledge-economy"&gt;Education Initiatives for Adoption: Empowering the Knowledge Economy&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly changing world, access to quality education is more important than ever. Education initiatives play a crucial role in shaping the future by equipping individuals with the knowledge and skills needed to thrive in a knowledge-driven economy. This matters to the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) movement because education is the cornerstone of verifiable knowledge, which is the currency that powers our platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Education Initiatives for Adoption — Daily KBC Note (2026-01-29)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-29-education-initiatives-for-adoption/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:49:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-29-education-initiatives-for-adoption/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="education-initiatives-for-adoption-shaping-a-knowledge-driven-world"&gt;Education Initiatives for Adoption: Shaping a Knowledge-Driven World&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced and ever-evolving world, the importance of education cannot be overstated. It is the key to unlocking opportunities, fostering innovation, and driving societal progress. Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) recognizes the critical role of education in building a sustainable future and is committed to promoting education initiatives for adoption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="overview"&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Principles&lt;/strong&gt;: Education initiatives for adoption focus on leveraging technology and innovative approaches to enhance learning outcomes, promote lifelong learning, and bridge the digital divide.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;K-Chain&lt;/strong&gt;: The distributed ledger technology of K-Chain ensures the secure storage of educational records, certificates, and credentials, enabling individuals to showcase their expertise and skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LightWeb&lt;/strong&gt;: The decentralized network of LightWeb facilitates efficient sharing of educational resources, enabling access to quality education for all, regardless of geographical location or socioeconomic status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oracle AI&lt;/strong&gt;: The intelligent engine of Oracle AI validates and retrieves knowledge on demand, providing learners with accurate and up-to-date information to support their educational journey.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proof-of-Knowledge&lt;/strong&gt;: By rewarding contributors for their expertise through Proof-of-Knowledge, KBC incentivizes the sharing of valuable knowledge and promotes a culture of continuous learning and knowledge exchange.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="current-events"&gt;Current Events&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No recent news available.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>