<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Zero-Knowledge on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/zero-knowledge/</link><description>Recent content in Zero-Knowledge on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:56:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/zero-knowledge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Zero-knowledge Proofs in KBC — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-06)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-06-zero-knowledge-proofs-in-kbc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:56:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-06-zero-knowledge-proofs-in-kbc/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="unveiling-the-power-of-zero-knowledge-proofs-in-kbc"&gt;Unveiling the Power of Zero-Knowledge Proofs in KBC&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the realm of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC), the concept of zero-knowledge proofs holds immense significance. Zero-knowledge proofs allow one party (the prover) to prove to another party (the verifier) that a statement is true without revealing any information beyond the fact that the statement is indeed true. This cryptographic technique is crucial in ensuring the security and privacy of transactions and interactions within the KBC ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Zero-knowledge Proofs in KBC — Daily KBC Note (2025-12-09)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-09-zero-knowledge-proofs-in-kbc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 06:33:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-09-zero-knowledge-proofs-in-kbc/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="zero-knowledge-proofs-in-kbc-unlocking-the-power-of-privacy-and-security"&gt;Zero-knowledge Proofs in KBC: Unlocking the Power of Privacy and Security&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine being able to prove a fact without revealing the underlying information. This is the magic of zero-knowledge proofs, a cryptographic method that allows one party (the prover) to convince another party (the verifier) of the truth of a statement without disclosing any additional details. In the context of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC), zero-knowledge proofs play a crucial role in ensuring the privacy and security of knowledge transactions.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>