<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>LightWeb on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/lightweb/</link><description>Recent content in LightWeb on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/lightweb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LightWeb (Decentralized Web Layer) — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-05)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-05-lightweb-decentralized-web-layer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-05-lightweb-decentralized-web-layer/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="illuminating-the-decentralized-web-lightweb-and-its-role-in-the-kbc-ecosystem"&gt;Illuminating the Decentralized Web: LightWeb and its Role in the KBC Ecosystem&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the realm of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC), LightWeb stands as a beacon of decentralized information exchange, enabling the seamless sharing of knowledge across the globe. This innovative layer plays a crucial role in facilitating the flow of verifiable knowledge within the KBC ecosystem, ultimately contributing to the creation of a trustworthy and inclusive knowledge economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="overview"&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Principles:&lt;/strong&gt; LightWeb operates as a decentralized network that enables efficient sharing of information among users within the KBC platform. It serves as a vital component in the transmission of knowledge claims stored on the K-Chain, providing a secure and reliable infrastructure for the exchange of verifiable expertise.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>LightWeb (Decentralized Web Layer) — Daily KBC Note (2025-11-28)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-11-28-lightweb-decentralized-web-layer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 06:32:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-11-28-lightweb-decentralized-web-layer/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="lightweb-decentralized-web-layer"&gt;LightWeb (Decentralized Web Layer)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the world of LightWeb, the decentralized web layer that plays a crucial role in the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project. Imagine LightWeb as the invisible threads that connect all the pieces of the KBC puzzle, allowing information to flow freely and securely across the network. In a digital landscape filled with centralized platforms and gatekeepers, LightWeb stands out as a beacon of decentralization, empowering users to share knowledge without intermediaries.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>