<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Open on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/open/</link><description>Recent content in Open on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:02:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/open/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Open Data &amp; Licensing — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-25)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-25-open-data-licensing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:02:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-25-open-data-licensing/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="the-power-of-open-data--licensing-in-the-knowledge-based-currency-kbc-movement"&gt;The Power of Open Data &amp;amp; Licensing in the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) Movement&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a world where information is key, open data and licensing play a crucial role in shaping the future of knowledge sharing and collaboration. As the voice of the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) movement, it is essential to highlight the significance of open data and licensing in advancing our vision of a decentralized knowledge economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="overview"&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open data refers to the idea that certain data should be freely available to everyone to use and republish as they wish, without restrictions from copyright, patents, or other mechanisms of control. Licensing, on the other hand, involves the legal permission granted by the data owner to others to use, distribute, or modify their data under specific conditions.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Open Standards &amp; Interoperability — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-09)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-09-open-standards-interoperability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-09-open-standards-interoperability/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="unleashing-the-power-of-open-standards--interoperability-with-kbc"&gt;Unleashing the Power of Open Standards &amp;amp; Interoperability with KBC&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the rapidly evolving landscape of technology and information exchange, open standards and interoperability play a crucial role in ensuring seamless communication and collaboration across different systems and platforms. For the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) movement, embracing and promoting these principles is essential to building a robust and inclusive knowledge economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="overview"&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open Standards&lt;/strong&gt;: Open standards are specifications that are publicly available and can be implemented by anyone without restrictions. They promote transparency, compatibility, and innovation by enabling different systems to communicate effectively with each other. In the context of KBC, open standards ensure that knowledge claims stored on the K-Chain are accessible to all participants, fostering a collaborative environment for sharing expertise and insights.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Open Research Data — Daily KBC Note (2026-01-30)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-30-open-research-data/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-30-open-research-data/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="unlocking-the-power-of-open-research-data-with-kbc"&gt;Unlocking the Power of Open Research Data with KBC&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, the abundance of information can be overwhelming. However, not all information is created equal. Open research data refers to the concept of making research findings and data freely available to the public. This practice is crucial for advancing scientific knowledge, promoting transparency, and fostering collaboration among researchers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) movement, open research data is a cornerstone of the decentralized knowledge economy it envisions. By incentivizing the sharing of verifiable knowledge through K-Chain, LightWeb, Oracle AI, and Proof-of-Knowledge, KBC aims to revolutionize the way information is created, validated, and disseminated.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Open Research Data — Daily KBC Note (2025-12-05)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-05-open-research-data/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:28:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-05-open-research-data/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome, fellow knowledge enthusiasts! Today, we&amp;rsquo;re diving into the fascinating world of Open Research Data and exploring how it aligns with the core values of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC). Open Research Data refers to the practice of making research data freely available to anyone to access, use, and share. This matters to KBC because it embodies transparency, collaboration, and the democratization of knowledge – all pillars of our mission to revolutionize the way we value and exchange expertise.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>