<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Archiving on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/archiving/</link><description>Recent content in Archiving on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 18:34:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/archiving/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Archiving &amp; Preservation — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-28)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-28-archiving-preservation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 18:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-28-archiving-preservation/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="blog-post-archiving--preservation-in-the-knowledge-based-currency-kbc-movement"&gt;Blog Post: Archiving &amp;amp; Preservation in the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) Movement&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world where information is constantly being created and shared, the importance of archiving and preservation cannot be overstated. Archiving is the process of storing and maintaining historical records and documents, while preservation involves ensuring the longevity and accessibility of these materials for future generations. In the context of the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) movement, archiving and preservation play a crucial role in creating a reliable and verifiable knowledge base that can be used to drive innovation and progress.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Archiving &amp; Preservation — Daily KBC Note (2025-12-08)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-08-archiving-preservation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-08-archiving-preservation/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="archiving--preservation-safeguarding-knowledge-for-generations"&gt;Archiving &amp;amp; Preservation: Safeguarding Knowledge for Generations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the digital age, the importance of archiving and preservation cannot be overstated. Just like ancient civilizations meticulously recorded their knowledge on durable materials to pass down to future generations, KBC recognizes the value of safeguarding knowledge for the long term. Archiving and preservation ensure that valuable information remains accessible and intact, serving as the foundation of a thriving knowledge economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="overview-key-principles-and-kbcs-foundations"&gt;Overview: Key Principles and KBC&amp;rsquo;s Foundations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Archiving&lt;/strong&gt;: Archiving involves the systematic storage and maintenance of information for future reference. It ensures that knowledge remains available even as technologies evolve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preservation&lt;/strong&gt;: Preservation focuses on protecting information from degradation or loss. It involves strategies to maintain the integrity and usability of knowledge over time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KBC&amp;rsquo;s foundations align seamlessly with the principles of archiving and preservation:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>