<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Ethics on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/ethics/</link><description>Recent content in Ethics on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 07:04:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/ethics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethics of AI &amp; Knowledge — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-16)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-16-ethics-of-ai-knowledge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 07:04:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-16-ethics-of-ai-knowledge/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="the-ethics-of-ai--knowledge-a-kbc-perspective"&gt;The Ethics of AI &amp;amp; Knowledge: A KBC Perspective&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly advancing technological landscape, the ethical implications of artificial intelligence (AI) and knowledge management have become increasingly important. As the voice of the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) movement, it is crucial to explore how these ethical considerations intersect with our mission to create a trustworthy, inclusive knowledge economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="overview"&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ethics in AI and knowledge involves examining the moral and societal implications of how information is gathered, processed, and utilized. Key principles include:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Ethics of AI &amp; Knowledge — Daily KBC Note (2025-11-29)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-11-29-ethics-of-ai-knowledge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 18:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-11-29-ethics-of-ai-knowledge/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="ethics-of-ai--knowledge-nurturing-the-soul-of-kbc"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ethics of AI &amp;amp; Knowledge: Nurturing the Soul of KBC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the age of artificial intelligence (AI) and vast amounts of data, the ethical implications of how knowledge is created, shared, and validated have never been more crucial. As a pioneering platform that values verifiable knowledge as a digital asset, Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) is deeply invested in upholding ethical standards in AI and knowledge management. By exploring the intersection of ethics, AI, and knowledge, we can navigate the complex landscape of information with integrity and responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>