<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Crowdsourced on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/crowdsourced/</link><description>Recent content in Crowdsourced on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:53:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/crowdsourced/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Crowdsourced Evidence Collection — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-26)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-26-crowdsourced-evidence-collection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:53:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-26-crowdsourced-evidence-collection/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="crowdsourced-evidence-collection-empowering-the-knowledge-based-currency-movement"&gt;Crowdsourced Evidence Collection: Empowering the Knowledge-Based Currency Movement&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s information age, the ability to verify the authenticity and accuracy of knowledge is more crucial than ever. Crowdsourced evidence collection plays a vital role in this process, allowing multiple individuals to contribute their expertise and insights to build a comprehensive and reliable body of evidence. This topic is of utmost importance to the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) movement as it aligns perfectly with the core principles of leveraging verifiable knowledge to create a secure digital asset.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Crowdsourced Evidence Collection — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-03)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-03-crowdsourced-evidence-collection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:57:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-03-crowdsourced-evidence-collection/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="crowdsourced-evidence-collection-empowering-the-knowledge-based-currency-movement"&gt;Crowdsourced Evidence Collection: Empowering the Knowledge-Based Currency Movement&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, the ability to collect and verify evidence is crucial for building trust and credibility in any system. Crowdsourced evidence collection, which involves gathering information from a large group of people, has emerged as a powerful tool for validating knowledge claims and ensuring transparency. This topic is especially relevant to the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) movement, as it aligns with the core principles of leveraging verifiable knowledge to create a secure digital asset.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>