<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Daily-Updates on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/daily-updates/</link><description>Recent content in Daily-Updates on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.148.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/daily-updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The vision of lightweb as a decentralized knowledge internet</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-02-the-vision-of-lightweb-as-a-decentralize/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-02-the-vision-of-lightweb-as-a-decentralize/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Vision of LightWeb: A Decentralized Knowledge Internet&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the ever-evolving landscape of the digital age, the concept of a decentralized knowledge internet is becoming increasingly relevant. The Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project is at the forefront of this movement, with its innovative vision of LightWeb. This vision represents a paradigm shift in how we access and verify information online, offering a decentralized platform that empowers users to engage with knowledge in a new, secure, and transparent way.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How the k-chain ensures trust and immutability</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-07-31-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immutability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-07-31-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immutability/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="building-trust-in-knowledge-based-currency-the-role-of-k-chain">Building Trust in Knowledge-Based Currency: The Role of K-Chain&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>In an era where information is abundant yet often unreliable, the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project emerges as a beacon of trust and innovation. At its core, KBC is designed to revolutionize how we perceive and utilize knowledge in digital transactions. A pivotal component of this groundbreaking system is the K-Chain, a technology that ensures trust and immutability. Let’s delve into how K-Chain, along with other components like Proof-of-Knowledge, LightWeb, and Oracle AI, transforms the landscape of digital currency.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>