<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Open on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/open/</link><description>Recent content in Open on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:43:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/open/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Open Research Data — Daily KBC Note (2026-01-30)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-30-open-research-data/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-30-open-research-data/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="unlocking-the-power-of-open-research-data-with-kbc"&gt;Unlocking the Power of Open Research Data with KBC&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, the abundance of information can be overwhelming. However, not all information is created equal. Open research data refers to the concept of making research findings and data freely available to the public. This practice is crucial for advancing scientific knowledge, promoting transparency, and fostering collaboration among researchers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) movement, open research data is a cornerstone of the decentralized knowledge economy it envisions. By incentivizing the sharing of verifiable knowledge through K-Chain, LightWeb, Oracle AI, and Proof-of-Knowledge, KBC aims to revolutionize the way information is created, validated, and disseminated.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Open Research Data — Daily KBC Note (2025-12-05)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-05-open-research-data/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:28:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-05-open-research-data/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome, fellow knowledge enthusiasts! Today, we&amp;rsquo;re diving into the fascinating world of Open Research Data and exploring how it aligns with the core values of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC). Open Research Data refers to the practice of making research data freely available to anyone to access, use, and share. This matters to KBC because it embodies transparency, collaboration, and the democratization of knowledge – all pillars of our mission to revolutionize the way we value and exchange expertise.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>