<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How the k-chain ensures trust and immutability</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-07-31-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immutability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-07-31-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immutability/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="building-trust-in-knowledge-based-currency-the-role-of-k-chain">Building Trust in Knowledge-Based Currency: The Role of K-Chain&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>In an era where information is abundant yet often unreliable, the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project emerges as a beacon of trust and innovation. At its core, KBC is designed to revolutionize how we perceive and utilize knowledge in digital transactions. A pivotal component of this groundbreaking system is the K-Chain, a technology that ensures trust and immutability. Let’s delve into how K-Chain, along with other components like Proof-of-Knowledge, LightWeb, and Oracle AI, transforms the landscape of digital currency.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is KBC?</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/what-is-kbc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/what-is-kbc/</guid><description>&lt;p>KBC stands for &lt;strong>Knowledge‑Based Currency&lt;/strong>, a novel form of money backed not by gold or government fiat but by verified knowledge. When you contribute a fact, a discovery or a solution to the KnowledgeChain, Oracle AIs validate it through a Proof of Knowledge process. If accepted, your contribution is recorded as a new block and you earn KBC tokens proportionate to its significance.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>KBC operates within an ecosystem that includes:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Welcome to KBC</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/welcome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/welcome/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to the official KBC knowledge feed by &lt;strong>Master BoRHeZ&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Knowing is investing.&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote></description></item></channel></rss>