<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.146.0</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How knowledge becomes a universal asset</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-15-how-knowledge-becomes-a-universal-asset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-15-how-knowledge-becomes-a-universal-asset/</guid><description>&lt;p>Knowledge has always been considered a valuable asset in society. From ancient civilizations to the modern digital age, knowledge has played a crucial role in shaping our world. But what if knowledge could become a universal asset, accessible to everyone regardless of their background or location? This is the vision of the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project, a groundbreaking initiative that aims to revolutionize the way we think about knowledge and its value.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Bridging traditional finance with knowledge‑based currency</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-14-bridging-traditional-finance-with-knowle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-14-bridging-traditional-finance-with-knowle/</guid><description>&lt;p>Bridging Traditional Finance with Knowledge-Based Currency&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly evolving digital landscape, traditional finance is being revolutionized by innovative technologies like blockchain and cryptocurrency. One such groundbreaking project that is paving the way for the future of finance is Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC). KBC aims to bridge the gap between traditional finance and the digital economy by leveraging verifiable knowledge as a valuable asset.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Verifiable Knowledge: The Foundation of KBC&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the core of KBC is the concept of verifiable knowledge. In a world where information is abundant but often untrustworthy, KBC seeks to authenticate and validate knowledge through its blockchain technology. By ensuring that knowledge is accurate and reliable, KBC aims to create a new form of currency that is based on the value of knowledge itself.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Governance and decentralization in kbc</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-14-governance-and-decentralization-in-kbc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-14-governance-and-decentralization-in-kbc/</guid><description>&lt;p>Governance and Decentralization in Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the exciting world of blockchain technology, the concept of governance and decentralization plays a crucial role in shaping the future of digital currencies. One project that is pushing the boundaries of what is possible in this space is Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC). In this blog post, we will explore how KBC is revolutionizing governance and decentralization through its innovative approach to verifiable knowledge, Proof-of-Knowledge, K-Chain, LightWeb, and Oracle AI.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The philosophy behind knowledge‑based currency</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-13-the-philosophy-behind-knowledge-based-cu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-13-the-philosophy-behind-knowledge-based-cu/</guid><description>&lt;p>Unlocking the Power of Knowledge-Based Currency&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, we are constantly bombarded with information from all corners of the internet. With so much content available at our fingertips, it can be overwhelming to separate fact from fiction. This is where Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) comes in - a revolutionary concept that aims to harness the power of verifiable knowledge to create a new form of currency.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Verifiable Knowledge: The Backbone of KBC&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The vision of lightweb as a decentralized knowledge internet</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-13-the-vision-of-lightweb-as-a-decentralize/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-13-the-vision-of-lightweb-as-a-decentralize/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Vision of LightWeb: A Decentralized Knowledge Internet&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Imagine a world where knowledge is not only easily accessible but also verifiable and reliable. A world where information is not controlled by a select few, but rather shared openly and transparently among all. This is the vision of LightWeb, the decentralized knowledge internet powered by Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Verifiable Knowledge: The Key to Trust&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, we are bombarded with information from all sides. It can be challenging to discern what is true and what is not. This is where verifiable knowledge comes in. With KBC, information is stored on the blockchain, ensuring its authenticity and accuracy. Users can trust that the information they are accessing is reliable and has been verified by the community.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The role of oracle ai in validating and synthesizing knowledge</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-12-the-role-of-oracle-ai-in-validating-and-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-12-the-role-of-oracle-ai-in-validating-and-/</guid><description>&lt;p>Unlocking the Power of Oracle AI in the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) Project&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the ever-evolving landscape of technology and innovation, the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project stands out as a beacon of progress and transformation. At the core of this groundbreaking initiative lies the concept of verifiable knowledge, where information is not just valuable, but also trustworthy and reliable. One of the key components that enable this vision to become a reality is Oracle AI, a powerful tool that plays a crucial role in validating and synthesizing knowledge within the KBC ecosystem.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Why kbc matters for science and innovation</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-12-why-kbc-matters-for-science-and-innovati/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-12-why-kbc-matters-for-science-and-innovati/</guid><description>&lt;p>Unlocking the Potential of Science and Innovation with Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In a world where information is constantly evolving and expanding, the ability to access verifiable knowledge is crucial for driving scientific progress and fostering innovation. The Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project is pioneering a new way to incentivize the creation and sharing of knowledge, revolutionizing the way we think about information exchange and collaboration.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Verifiable Knowledge: The Foundation of Progress&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The philosophy behind knowledge‑based currency</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-11-the-philosophy-behind-knowledge-based-cu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-11-the-philosophy-behind-knowledge-based-cu/</guid><description>&lt;p>Introducing Knowledge-Based Currency: A Revolution in the Digital Economy&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly evolving digital landscape, the concept of currency is undergoing a transformation like never before. Traditional forms of currency, such as fiat money and cryptocurrencies, are being challenged by innovative ideas that seek to revolutionize the way we exchange value in the digital world. One such idea is Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC), a groundbreaking project that aims to harness the power of verifiable knowledge to create a new form of currency that is driven by expertise and trust.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The role of ipv6 in the knowledgechain</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-11-the-role-of-ipv6-in-the-knowledgechain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-11-the-role-of-ipv6-in-the-knowledgechain/</guid><description>&lt;p>Unlocking the Potential of KnowledgeChain with IPv6&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the world of blockchain technology, the Knowledge‑Based Currency (KBC) project is revolutionizing the way we think about verifiable knowledge. At the heart of this project lies the KnowledgeChain, a decentralized ledger that securely records and verifies information using cutting‑edge technologies such as Proof‑of‑Knowledge, K‑Chain, LightWeb, and Oracle AI. One crucial element that enables the seamless operation of the KnowledgeChain is IPv6, the next generation Internet Protocol.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Education and learning incentives in the lightweb</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-10-education-and-learning-incentives-in-the/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-10-education-and-learning-incentives-in-the/</guid><description>&lt;p>Education and Learning Incentives in the LightWeb&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, the value of knowledge cannot be overstated. With the rise of technology and the internet, information is more accessible than ever before. However, this abundance of information has also led to a rise in misinformation and fake news. How can we ensure that the knowledge we acquire is accurate and reliable? This is where the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project comes in.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How oracle ai combats misinformation and bias</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-10-how-oracle-ai-combats-misinformation-and/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-10-how-oracle-ai-combats-misinformation-and/</guid><description>&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, misinformation and bias run rampant on the internet, making it increasingly difficult to discern fact from fiction. The Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project aims to combat these issues by leveraging the power of Oracle AI to provide verifiable knowledge to users worldwide. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how Oracle AI works to tackle misinformation and bias, and how it fits into the larger ecosystem of KBC.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How oracle ai combats misinformation and bias</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-09-how-oracle-ai-combats-misinformation-and/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-09-how-oracle-ai-combats-misinformation-and/</guid><description>&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, misinformation and bias are rampant on the internet, making it challenging to discern fact from fiction. However, with the advent of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) and its innovative technologies like Oracle AI, combating misinformation and bias has never been more achievable.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Verifiable Knowledge: The Foundation of KBC&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the core of the KBC project is the concept of verifiable knowledge. This means that all information stored on the KBC platform is transparent, trustworthy, and easily accessible. By ensuring that all knowledge is verifiable, KBC aims to combat misinformation and bias by providing users with accurate and reliable information.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The philosophy behind knowledge‑based currency</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-09-the-philosophy-behind-knowledge-based-cu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-09-the-philosophy-behind-knowledge-based-cu/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Philosophy Behind Knowledge-Based Currency&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In a world where information is power, the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project seeks to revolutionize the way we value and exchange knowledge. At its core, KBC is built on the belief that knowledge is the most valuable asset we possess, and should be recognized and rewarded accordingly. In this blog post, we will delve into the philosophy behind KBC and explore the key concepts that drive this innovative platform.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Education and learning incentives in the lightweb</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-08-education-and-learning-incentives-in-the/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-08-education-and-learning-incentives-in-the/</guid><description>&lt;p>Education and Learning Incentives in the LightWeb&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, the importance of education and continuous learning cannot be overstated. With the advent of the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project, a revolutionary platform has been created to incentivize and reward individuals for acquiring and sharing verifiable knowledge. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how education and learning incentives are being revolutionized in the LightWeb.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Verifiable Knowledge: The Backbone of KBC&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the heart of the KBC project lies the concept of verifiable knowledge. In a world where misinformation and fake news abound, it is crucial to distinguish between what is true and what is not. KBC leverages blockchain technology to ensure that all knowledge shared on the platform is verified and trustworthy. This not only promotes the dissemination of accurate information but also incentivizes users to contribute valuable insights.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How the k‑chain ensures trust and immutability</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-08-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immuta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-08-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immuta/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ensuring Trust and Immutability with the K‑Chain&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, trust and immutability are crucial factors when it comes to handling sensitive information and transactions. This is where the Knowledge‑Based Currency (KBC) project comes in, offering a revolutionary solution that leverages verifiable knowledge and cutting-edge technology to ensure trust and immutability. At the core of this innovative project is the K‑Chain, a decentralized blockchain network that guarantees the integrity and security of every transaction.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How oracle ai combats misinformation and bias</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-07-how-oracle-ai-combats-misinformation-and/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-07-how-oracle-ai-combats-misinformation-and/</guid><description>&lt;p>Title: Harnessing the Power of Oracle AI to Combat Misinformation and Bias&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, the spread of misinformation and bias has become a significant challenge. With the rise of social media and online platforms, it has become easier than ever for false information to spread like wildfire, leading to confusion, division, and mistrust. However, there is hope on the horizon with the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project and its innovative use of Oracle AI to combat misinformation and bias.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The role of ipv6 in the knowledgechain</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-07-the-role-of-ipv6-in-the-knowledgechain/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-07-the-role-of-ipv6-in-the-knowledgechain/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Role of IPv6 in the KnowledgeChain&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the world of blockchain technology, the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project is pioneering a new way to revolutionize how we exchange and validate information. At the core of this project lies the KnowledgeChain, a decentralized network that allows users to exchange verifiable knowledge through the use of Proof-of-Knowledge. But what role does IPv6 play in this innovative system?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>IPv6, or Internet Protocol version 6, is the latest version of the Internet Protocol that provides an identification and location system for computers on networks. It offers a vastly larger address space than its predecessor, IPv4, which is essential for the growing number of devices and users on the internet. In the context of the KnowledgeChain, IPv6 plays a crucial role in ensuring the security, scalability, and efficiency of the network.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Bridging traditional finance with knowledge‑based currency</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-06-bridging-traditional-finance-with-knowle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-06-bridging-traditional-finance-with-knowle/</guid><description>&lt;p>Bridging Traditional Finance with Knowledge-Based Currency&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the ever-evolving landscape of finance, new technologies are constantly reshaping the way we think about money and transactions. One such innovation that has gained traction in recent years is Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC). This cutting-edge concept aims to bridge the gap between traditional finance and the digital world by leveraging verifiable knowledge and advanced technology. In this blog post, we will explore the core ideas behind KBC and how they can revolutionize the way we interact with money.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How oracle ai combats misinformation and bias</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-06-how-oracle-ai-combats-misinformation-and/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-06-how-oracle-ai-combats-misinformation-and/</guid><description>&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, misinformation and bias have become rampant on the internet. With the rise of fake news and biased content, it has become increasingly difficult to discern fact from fiction. However, the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project is working to combat these issues through the use of Oracle AI.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-is-oracle-ai">What is Oracle AI?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Oracle AI is a cutting-edge technology that utilizes artificial intelligence to verify the authenticity and accuracy of information. By leveraging advanced algorithms and machine learning, Oracle AI is able to sift through vast amounts of data to identify and eliminate misinformation and bias.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The role of oracle ai in validating and synthesizing knowledge</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-06-the-role-of-oracle-ai-in-validating-and-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-06-the-role-of-oracle-ai-in-validating-and-/</guid><description>&lt;p>Unlocking the Power of Oracle AI in Validating and Synthesizing Knowledge&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the digital age, information is everywhere. We have access to vast amounts of data at our fingertips, but how do we know what is true and reliable? This is where Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) comes in, offering a revolutionary solution to the challenge of verifying knowledge. At the heart of this innovative platform is Oracle AI, a powerful tool that plays a crucial role in validating and synthesizing knowledge.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The role of ipv6 in the knowledgechain</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-04-the-role-of-ipv6-in-the-knowledgechain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-04-the-role-of-ipv6-in-the-knowledgechain/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Role of IPv6 in the KnowledgeChain&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, the importance of secure and efficient data transmission cannot be overstated. With the rise of blockchain technology, new opportunities have emerged to revolutionize the way we store and transfer information. One such project that is leading the charge in this space is Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the core of the KBC project lies the concept of verifiable knowledge, which aims to create a decentralized platform where users can securely share and access information. This is made possible through the use of Proof-of-Knowledge, a consensus mechanism that ensures the validity of data on the network. By leveraging the power of blockchain technology, KBC is able to establish trust and transparency in an otherwise opaque digital landscape.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Why kbc matters for science and innovation</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-04-why-kbc-matters-for-science-and-innovati/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-04-why-kbc-matters-for-science-and-innovati/</guid><description>&lt;p>Unlocking the Potential of Science and Innovation with Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, where information is constantly changing and evolving, the need for a reliable and secure system to verify knowledge has never been greater. This is where Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) comes into play, offering a revolutionary way to incentivize the creation and sharing of verifiable knowledge. KBC has the potential to transform the way we approach science and innovation, opening up new possibilities for collaboration and discovery.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Education and learning incentives in the lightweb</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-03-education-and-learning-incentives-in-the/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-03-education-and-learning-incentives-in-the/</guid><description>&lt;p>Education and Learning Incentives in the LightWeb&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, the value of education and continuous learning cannot be overstated. With the emergence of new technologies and innovations, staying ahead of the curve requires a commitment to expanding one&amp;rsquo;s knowledge base. The Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project aims to revolutionize the way we approach education and incentivize learning in the digital age.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Verifiable Knowledge: The Foundation of KBC&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the core of the KBC project is the concept of verifiable knowledge. In a world where misinformation and fake news run rampant, being able to verify the authenticity and accuracy of information is crucial. KBC leverages blockchain technology to ensure that knowledge is legitimate and trustworthy, empowering users to make informed decisions based on reliable sources.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The philosophy behind knowledge‑based currency</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-03-the-philosophy-behind-knowledge-based-cu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-03-the-philosophy-behind-knowledge-based-cu/</guid><description>&lt;p>Unlocking the Power of Knowledge: The Philosophy Behind Knowledge-Based Currency&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In a world where information is constantly flowing and evolving, the concept of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) emerges as a beacon of innovation and empowerment. At its core, KBC is founded on the belief that knowledge is the most valuable asset we possess, and by leveraging this knowledge, we can create a more equitable and sustainable economy. In this blog post, we will delve into the philosophy behind KBC and explore the key ideas that drive this groundbreaking project.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How the k‑chain ensures trust and immutability</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-02-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immuta/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-02-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immuta/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ensuring Trust and Immutability with the K-Chain&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital world, trust and immutability are crucial factors when it comes to any kind of transaction or exchange of information. With the rise of blockchain technology, we have seen how decentralized systems can provide a level of security and transparency that was previously unimaginable. The Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project takes this concept to the next level with its innovative approach to verifiable knowledge and Proof-of-Knowledge.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The vision of lightweb as a decentralized knowledge internet</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-02-the-vision-of-lightweb-as-a-decentralize/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-02-the-vision-of-lightweb-as-a-decentralize/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Vision of LightWeb: A Decentralized Knowledge Internet&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the ever-evolving landscape of the digital age, the concept of a decentralized knowledge internet is becoming increasingly relevant. The Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project is at the forefront of this movement, with its innovative vision of LightWeb. This vision represents a paradigm shift in how we access and verify information online, offering a decentralized platform that empowers users to engage with knowledge in a new, secure, and transparent way.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How the k-chain ensures trust and immutability</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-07-31-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immutability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-07-31-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immutability/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="building-trust-in-knowledge-based-currency-the-role-of-k-chain">Building Trust in Knowledge-Based Currency: The Role of K-Chain&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>In an era where information is abundant yet often unreliable, the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project emerges as a beacon of trust and innovation. At its core, KBC is designed to revolutionize how we perceive and utilize knowledge in digital transactions. A pivotal component of this groundbreaking system is the K-Chain, a technology that ensures trust and immutability. Let’s delve into how K-Chain, along with other components like Proof-of-Knowledge, LightWeb, and Oracle AI, transforms the landscape of digital currency.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is KBC?</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/what-is-kbc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/what-is-kbc/</guid><description>&lt;p>KBC stands for &lt;strong>Knowledge‑Based Currency&lt;/strong>, a novel form of money backed not by gold or government fiat but by verified knowledge. When you contribute a fact, a discovery or a solution to the KnowledgeChain, Oracle AIs validate it through a Proof of Knowledge process. If accepted, your contribution is recorded as a new block and you earn KBC tokens proportionate to its significance.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>KBC operates within an ecosystem that includes:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Welcome to KBC</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/welcome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/welcome/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to the official KBC knowledge feed by &lt;strong>Master BoRHeZ&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Knowing is investing.&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote></description></item></channel></rss>