<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome to Knowledge-Based Currency on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome to Knowledge-Based Currency on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How the k-chain ensures trust and immutability</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-07-31-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immutability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-07-31-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immutability/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="building-trust-in-knowledge-based-currency-the-role-of-k-chain">Building Trust in Knowledge-Based Currency: The Role of K-Chain&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>In an era where information is abundant yet often unreliable, the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project emerges as a beacon of trust and innovation. At its core, KBC is designed to revolutionize how we perceive and utilize knowledge in digital transactions. A pivotal component of this groundbreaking system is the K-Chain, a technology that ensures trust and immutability. Let’s delve into how K-Chain, along with other components like Proof-of-Knowledge, LightWeb, and Oracle AI, transforms the landscape of digital currency.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is KBC?</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/what-is-kbc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/what-is-kbc/</guid><description>&lt;p>KBC stands for &lt;strong>Knowledge‑Based Currency&lt;/strong>, a novel form of money backed not by gold or government fiat but by verified knowledge. When you contribute a fact, a discovery or a solution to the KnowledgeChain, Oracle AIs validate it through a Proof of Knowledge process. If accepted, your contribution is recorded as a new block and you earn KBC tokens proportionate to its significance.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>KBC operates within an ecosystem that includes:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Welcome to KBC</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/welcome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/welcome/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to the official KBC knowledge feed by &lt;strong>Master BoRHeZ&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Knowing is investing.&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://borhez.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Master BoRHeZ&lt;/strong> is the visionary behind Knowledge‑Based Currency. An engineer, therapist and perpetual traveler, he believes that our monetary systems should reflect and reward the creation of knowledge. KBC began as an idea to align economics with truth and has evolved into a comprehensive ecosystem built on the K‑Chain ledger and supported by Oracle AIs.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="mission">Mission&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Our mission is to create a stable, transparent currency backed by verified knowledge. By encouraging contributions from anyone—individuals or AI—the KBC ecosystem promotes continuous learning and collective intelligence. Every piece of validated knowledge increases the value of the system.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://borhez.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/contact/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="help-build-a-universal-knowledge-system">Help build a universal knowledge system&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>We’re always looking for collaborators, developers, researchers and thought leaders to join the KBC project. Use the form below or send us a message directly to become part of the community.&lt;/p>
&lt;form action="https://formsubmit.co/borhezgames@gmail.com" method="POST" class="contact-form">
 &lt;!-- Customize the email subject -->
 &lt;input type="hidden" name="_subject" value="New KBC website contact" />
&lt;p>&lt;label for="alias">Alias (optional):&lt;/label>&lt;br>
&lt;input type="text" id="alias" name="alias">&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;label for="email">Email (required):&lt;/label>&lt;br>
&lt;input type="email" id="email" name="email"
required pattern="^[^@\s]+@[^@\s]+\.[^@\s]+$"
title="Please enter a valid email address">&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;label for="message">Message / Area of interest:&lt;/label>&lt;br>&lt;/p>
 &lt;textarea id="message" name="message" rows="5" cols="40" maxlength="750">&lt;/textarea>&lt;br>&lt;br>
 &lt;input type="submit" value="Send">
&lt;/form>
&lt;p>Your message will be sent directly to our team via email. We&amp;rsquo;ll be in touch soon.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Get Involved</title><link>https://borhez.com/get-involved/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/get-involved/</guid><description>&lt;p>The KBC ecosystem thrives on collaboration. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a developer, researcher, educator or curious thinker, there are many ways to participate:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Share knowledge:&lt;/strong> Contribute facts, datasets, algorithms or insights. The Oracle AI will validate your contributions and reward you with KBC.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Develop the MVS:&lt;/strong> Help build the FastAPI/Streamlit Minimum Viable System. Check out the &lt;code>KBC&lt;/code> folder in our repository for the current codebase.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Review our whitepapers:&lt;/strong> Provide feedback on the research documents listed in the &lt;a href="https://borhez.com/resources/">Resources&lt;/a> section.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Join the discussion:&lt;/strong> Engage with the community on our blog posts and forums (to be set up).&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>To get started, clone the repository, read through the documentation and reach out with your ideas. Together we can build a currency that values truth and fosters collective intelligence.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>LightWeb</title><link>https://borhez.com/lightweb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/lightweb/</guid><description>&lt;p>LightWeb is the decentralized &amp;ldquo;knowledge network&amp;rdquo; layer of KBC. It sits on top of the &lt;strong>KnowledgeChain&lt;/strong> ledger and provides a censorship‑resistant, truth‑indexed web of content. Instead of websites hosted on a central server, LightWeb distributes knowledge blocks across the network and indexes them by their semantic relationships.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Because every content unit is backed by verifiable knowledge, LightWeb can deliver search and browsing experiences where accuracy and trust are built in. The network encourages transparency, collaboration and open access. As the ecosystem evolves, LightWeb will become the foundation for decentralized applications that leverage KBC, Oracle AI and the K‑Chain.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Minimum Viable System</title><link>https://borhez.com/mvs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/mvs/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Minimum Viable System (MVS) demonstrates the core mechanics of KBC and the KnowledgeChain. It currently consists of a local &lt;strong>FastAPI&lt;/strong> backend with a &lt;strong>SQLite&lt;/strong> database and a &lt;strong>Streamlit&lt;/strong> frontend for interacting with users.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="components">Components&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>K‑Chain database&lt;/strong> – Stores knowledge blocks (“neurons”) with statements, tags, certainty levels and explicit links to related blocks.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Users &amp;amp; Ledger&lt;/strong> – Keeps track of user profiles and their KBC balances. Each time a validated knowledge block is added, the contributor’s balance increases.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Validator &amp;amp; Oracle placeholders&lt;/strong> – Validation logic is rudimentary in v2.1: blocks are marked as pending; future iterations will integrate Oracle AI and Proof‑of‑Knowledge【599027023887502†L175-L181】.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Teodora AI (Y‑Engine)&lt;/strong> – A planned module that will assist in knowledge validation, synthesis and KBC assignment.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="how-to-run-locally">How to run locally&lt;/h3>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Install Python 3.8+ and clone the repository (or use the &lt;code>KBC&lt;/code> folder in this site’s source).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Oracle AI</title><link>https://borhez.com/oracle-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/oracle-ai/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://borhez.com/images/oracle-ai-diagram.png#center" alt="Oracle AI conceptual diagram">&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="harnessing-collective-intelligence">Harnessing collective intelligence&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Oracle AI is an intelligent oracle that draws its insights from the authenticated knowledge recorded on the &lt;strong>K‑Chain&lt;/strong>. It acts as a bridge between human contributors and the digital ledger, verifying submissions, synthesizing new insights and answering questions.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Powered by advanced language models and rigorous validation, Oracle AI ensures that only verifiable facts enter the KnowledgeChain. Over time it will become a powerful search and discovery tool, enabling researchers and builders to access and reuse trusted knowledge. When combined with &lt;strong>LightWeb&lt;/strong> and the &lt;strong>MVS&lt;/strong>, Oracle AI helps turn raw information into a living knowledge economy.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Resources</title><link>https://borhez.com/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/resources/</guid><description>&lt;p>Below is a selection of key documents and whitepapers produced within the KBC project. They provide deeper insight into the philosophy, technology and roadmap behind Knowledge‑Based Currency.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>KBC.docx&lt;/strong> – detailed overview of KBC history, principles and technical backbone.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>KBC Genesis Block Creation.docx&lt;/strong> – analysis of the original KBC tokenomics and philosophical foundations.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>KnowledgeChain (K‑Chain) Whitepaper.docx&lt;/strong> – technical description of the K‑Chain ledger and its Proof of Knowledge consensus.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Building the LightWeb Research Plan.docx&lt;/strong> – roadmap for the decentralized LightWeb platform.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>What is KBC_.docx&lt;/strong> – introduction explaining KBC for newcomers (also available as a blog post).&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Next steps and roadmap (MVS v2.x Focus).docx&lt;/strong> – outlines features for the Minimum Viable System.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Teodora KBC MVS #U2013 Minimum Viable System.docx&lt;/strong> – documentation for the current MVS implementation.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Knowledge‑Based Currency – The Eternal Force of Value.docx&lt;/strong> – essay on why knowledge as currency endures.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Light of Knowledge.docx&lt;/strong> – exploration of the role of information in the LightWeb ecosystem.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>KBC K‑Chain Deep Research.docx&lt;/strong> – deeper dive into the network design and data structures.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Open Letter &amp;amp; Manifesto for Knowledge‑Based Currency.docx&lt;/strong> – calls for collaboration and outlines guiding principles.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>The Y‑Engine.docx&lt;/strong> – conceptual design for the Oracle AI that validates and synthesizes knowledge.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>PAIN.docx&lt;/strong> – internal research on challenges and pain points addressed by KBC.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>All files are located in the repository’s &lt;code>KBC/Resources&lt;/code> folder. Feel free to explore and contribute to future revisions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The KnowledgeChain (K‑Chain)</title><link>https://borhez.com/k-chain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/k-chain/</guid><description>&lt;p>The &lt;strong>K‑Chain&lt;/strong> is a decentralized, append‑only ledger inspired by blockchain technology. Instead of recording financial transactions, it stores &lt;strong>knowledge blocks&lt;/strong>—verified units of information such as facts, data sets or algorithms. Each block contains:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Content:&lt;/strong> the statement or dataset itself.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Metadata:&lt;/strong> information about the contributor, timestamp and related tags.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Links:&lt;/strong> references to other blocks, creating a network of related knowledge.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Blocks are validated through a &lt;strong>Proof of Knowledge&lt;/strong> process. Oracle AIs check that submissions are accurate, not duplicated and contribute value before adding them to the chain. Once accepted, blocks become immutable and publicly accessible, forming an ever‑expanding map of human and artificial intelligence.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>