<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Knowledge on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/knowledge/</link><description>Recent content in Knowledge on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 18:37:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/knowledge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Knowledge Blocks (KBs): Claims + Evidence — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-15)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-15-knowledge-blocks-kbs-claims-evidence/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 18:37:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-15-knowledge-blocks-kbs-claims-evidence/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="unleashing-the-power-of-knowledge-blocks-kbs-claims--evidence"&gt;Unleashing the Power of Knowledge Blocks (KBs): Claims + Evidence&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the world of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC), Knowledge Blocks (KBs) play a crucial role in transforming verifiable knowledge into a secure digital asset. KBs are the building blocks of the decentralized knowledge economy, where claims are backed by evidence, creating a transparent and trustworthy ecosystem. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive deep into the concept of KBs, exploring how they are shaping the future of information exchange and why they matter in the grand scheme of KBC.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Knowledge Blocks (KBs): Claims + Evidence — Daily KBC Note (2025-12-09)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-09-knowledge-blocks-kbs-claims-evidence/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 18:28:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-09-knowledge-blocks-kbs-claims-evidence/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="knowledge-blocks-kbs-claims--evidence"&gt;Knowledge Blocks (KBs): Claims + Evidence&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine a world where knowledge is not just a tool for personal growth but a valuable asset that can be securely stored, shared, and rewarded. This is the vision of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC), where Knowledge Blocks (KBs) play a crucial role in transforming information into digital currency. In this blog post, we will explore the concept of Knowledge Blocks, focusing on how claims and evidence come together to form the building blocks of a decentralized knowledge economy.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>