<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>User on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/user/</link><description>Recent content in User on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:53:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/user/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>User Experience Design in Decentralized Apps — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-04)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-04-user-experience-design-in-decentralized-apps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:53:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-04-user-experience-design-in-decentralized-apps/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="user-experience-design-in-decentralized-apps"&gt;User Experience Design in Decentralized Apps&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;User Experience (UX) design plays a crucial role in the success of any digital platform, and decentralized apps (dApps) are no exception. In the world of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC), ensuring a seamless and intuitive user experience is key to encouraging widespread adoption and engagement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="overview"&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Key principles of User Experience Design in decentralized apps include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplicity&lt;/strong&gt;: Designing interfaces that are easy to navigate and understand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consistency&lt;/strong&gt;: Maintaining uniformity in design elements and interactions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feedback&lt;/strong&gt;: Providing clear feedback to users on their actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accessibility&lt;/strong&gt;: Ensuring that the app is usable by individuals of all backgrounds and abilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the context of KBC, the components of the platform such as K-Chain, LightWeb, Oracle AI, and Proof-of-Knowledge are all interconnected to enhance the user experience. K-Chain stores immutable knowledge claims, LightWeb facilitates efficient information sharing, Oracle AI validates and retrieves knowledge, and Proof-of-Knowledge rewards contributors for their expertise.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>User Onboarding &amp; Support — Daily KBC Note (2025-12-04)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-04-user-onboarding-support/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:33:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-04-user-onboarding-support/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="user-onboarding--support-nurturing-the-growth-of-the-knowledge-economy"&gt;User Onboarding &amp;amp; Support: Nurturing the Growth of the Knowledge Economy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;User onboarding and support are crucial components for any platform&amp;rsquo;s success, and this holds true for Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) as well. In the context of KBC, user onboarding refers to the process of guiding new users through the platform and helping them understand how to engage with the ecosystem effectively. On the other hand, user support involves providing assistance and troubleshooting to existing users to ensure a seamless experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>