<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Tokenomics on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/tokenomics/</link><description>Recent content in Tokenomics on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:51:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/tokenomics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tokenomics of Knowledge-Based Currencies — Daily KBC Note (2026-01-30)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-30-tokenomics-of-knowledge-based-currencies/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-30-tokenomics-of-knowledge-based-currencies/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="tokenomics-of-knowledge-based-currencies"&gt;Tokenomics of Knowledge-Based Currencies&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the world of cryptocurrencies, tokenomics refers to the study of how tokens operate within a given ecosystem. It encompasses everything from the distribution and supply of tokens to how they are used and valued. When it comes to Knowledge-Based Currencies (KBC), tokenomics plays a crucial role in incentivizing the creation and sharing of verifiable knowledge, ultimately driving the growth of a decentralized knowledge economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="overview"&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;K-Chain&lt;/strong&gt;: This distributed ledger is the backbone of KBC, storing immutable knowledge claims securely. It ensures transparency and trust by recording every transaction and knowledge contribution on the network.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LightWeb&lt;/strong&gt;: A decentralized network that enables efficient sharing of information among users. It ensures that knowledge is accessible to everyone, regardless of geographical location or socioeconomic status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oracle AI&lt;/strong&gt;: The intelligent engine that validates and retrieves knowledge on demand. It acts as a gatekeeper, ensuring that only verified knowledge claims are rewarded within the ecosystem.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proof-of-Knowledge&lt;/strong&gt;: Unlike traditional cryptocurrencies that rely on proof of work or stake, KBC rewards users for their expertise and contributions to the knowledge economy. This incentivizes individuals to share their knowledge and skills, driving the growth of the platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="current-events"&gt;Current Events&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No recent news available.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>