<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Decentralized on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/decentralized/</link><description>Recent content in Decentralized on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 06:33:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/decentralized/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Decentralized Oracle Networks — Daily KBC Note (2025-12-04)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-04-decentralized-oracle-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 06:33:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-04-decentralized-oracle-networks/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="decentralized-oracle-networks-bridging-knowledge-and-blockchain"&gt;Decentralized Oracle Networks: Bridging Knowledge and Blockchain&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine a vast library where the shelves are filled not with dusty books, but with real-time, accurate information from around the world. This is the essence of Decentralized Oracle Networks, a crucial component of the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="overview"&gt;Overview&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Decentralized Oracle Networks act as bridges between the blockchain world and external sources of information, ensuring that smart contracts have access to real-world data. In the context of KBC, Oracle AI plays a pivotal role in validating and retrieving knowledge claims stored on the K-Chain. By tapping into these decentralized oracle networks, KBC can leverage the power of external knowledge sources in a secure and trustless manner.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Decentralized Governance Models — Daily KBC Note (2025-11-27)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-11-27-decentralized-governance-models/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 21:26:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-11-27-decentralized-governance-models/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="decentralized-governance-models-empowering-the-community"&gt;Decentralized Governance Models: Empowering the Community&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Decentralized governance models are at the heart of the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project, shaping how decisions are made and resources are allocated within the ecosystem. This topic is crucial for KBC because it ensures that power is distributed among participants rather than concentrated in the hands of a few. By enabling community members to have a say in the direction of the project, decentralized governance models foster transparency, inclusivity, and trust.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>