<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Token on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/token/</link><description>Recent content in Token on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:49:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/token/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Token Launch Strategies — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-22)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-22-token-launch-strategies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:49:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-22-token-launch-strategies/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="token-launch-strategies-paving-the-way-for-a-knowledge-based-currency-revolution"&gt;Token Launch Strategies: Paving the Way for a Knowledge-Based Currency Revolution&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the fast-paced world of cryptocurrency, token launch strategies play a crucial role in the success and sustainability of a project. For Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC), these strategies are not just about raising funds, but also about building a community of knowledgeable contributors and users who believe in the power of verifiable knowledge. In this blog post, we will delve into the importance of token launch strategies, how they align with K-Chain, LightWeb, Oracle AI, and Proof-of-Knowledge, and how recent global events highlight the need for a platform like KBC.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Token Gating &amp; Access Control — Daily KBC Note (2026-02-19)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-19-token-gating-access-control/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-02-19-token-gating-access-control/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="token-gating--access-control-empowering-the-knowledge-economy"&gt;Token Gating &amp;amp; Access Control: Empowering the Knowledge Economy&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the world of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC), the concept of Token Gating &amp;amp; Access Control plays a crucial role in ensuring the integrity and security of the platform. By understanding how this mechanism works, we can see how it not only safeguards valuable knowledge assets but also promotes a fair and inclusive knowledge economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="overview"&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Token Gating &amp;amp; Access Control is a system that regulates access to certain knowledge assets based on the possession of specific tokens or credentials. In the context of KBC, this means that users must possess a certain amount of KBC tokens or demonstrate their expertise through the Proof-of-Knowledge mechanism in order to access and contribute to the platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Token Launch Strategies — Daily KBC Note (2026-01-27)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-27-token-launch-strategies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-27-token-launch-strategies/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="token-launch-strategies-a-key-component-of-the-kbc-movement"&gt;Token Launch Strategies: A Key Component of the KBC Movement&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the world of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC), token launch strategies play a crucial role in shaping the success and sustainability of the platform. As KBC aims to revolutionize the way knowledge is shared and rewarded, it is essential to understand how token launches can drive adoption, incentivize participation, and ensure the integrity of the ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="overview"&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Token launch strategies involve the planning and execution of the initial distribution of tokens to users, investors, and stakeholders. This process is crucial for establishing the value of the token, creating liquidity, and building a vibrant community around the platform. In the context of KBC, token launch strategies are closely tied to the core principles of the platform:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>