<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Decentralized on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/decentralized/</link><description>Recent content in Decentralized on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:38:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/decentralized/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Decentralized Governance Models — Daily KBC Note (2026-01-28)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-28-decentralized-governance-models/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:38:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-28-decentralized-governance-models/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="decentralized-governance-models-shaping-a-fair-knowledge-economy"&gt;Decentralized Governance Models: Shaping a Fair Knowledge Economy&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s interconnected world, the need for transparent and accountable governance models has never been more critical. Decentralized governance models offer a promising solution to address the challenges of trust, security, and inclusivity in decision-making processes. This topic is of utmost importance to the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) movement as it aligns with our vision of creating a fair and trustworthy knowledge economy.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Decentralized Oracles vs. Centralized — Daily KBC Note (2026-01-26)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-26-decentralized-oracles-vs-centralized/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:37:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2026-01-26-decentralized-oracles-vs-centralized/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="decentralized-oracles-vs-centralized-a-vital-debate-for-the-knowledge-based-currency-kbc-movement"&gt;Decentralized Oracles vs. Centralized: A Vital Debate for the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) Movement&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the world of blockchain technology and decentralized platforms, the debate between decentralized oracles and centralized oracles is a crucial one. Oracles serve as bridges between the blockchain and the real world, providing external data and information to smart contracts. This topic is of utmost importance to the KBC movement as it directly impacts the reliability and integrity of the knowledge stored on K-Chain, the efficiency of information sharing on LightWeb, the accuracy of validations by Oracle AI, and the fairness of rewards through Proof-of-Knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Decentralized Peer Review — Daily KBC Note (2025-12-07)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-07-decentralized-peer-review/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 06:28:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-07-decentralized-peer-review/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Decentralized Peer Review is a crucial component of the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project, as it plays a vital role in ensuring the accuracy and reliability of the knowledge claims stored on the K-Chain ledger. By leveraging the power of a decentralized network of peers to validate and verify information, KBC is able to create a trustworthy ecosystem where expertise is rewarded and misinformation is minimized. In a world where misinformation runs rampant, decentralized peer review is a beacon of truth and integrity.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Decentralized Oracle Networks — Daily KBC Note (2025-12-04)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-04-decentralized-oracle-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 06:33:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-12-04-decentralized-oracle-networks/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="decentralized-oracle-networks-bridging-knowledge-and-blockchain"&gt;Decentralized Oracle Networks: Bridging Knowledge and Blockchain&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine a vast library where the shelves are filled not with dusty books, but with real-time, accurate information from around the world. This is the essence of Decentralized Oracle Networks, a crucial component of the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="overview"&gt;Overview&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Decentralized Oracle Networks act as bridges between the blockchain world and external sources of information, ensuring that smart contracts have access to real-world data. In the context of KBC, Oracle AI plays a pivotal role in validating and retrieving knowledge claims stored on the K-Chain. By tapping into these decentralized oracle networks, KBC can leverage the power of external knowledge sources in a secure and trustless manner.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Decentralized Governance Models — Daily KBC Note (2025-11-27)</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-11-27-decentralized-governance-models/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 21:26:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-11-27-decentralized-governance-models/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="decentralized-governance-models-empowering-the-community"&gt;Decentralized Governance Models: Empowering the Community&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Decentralized governance models are at the heart of the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project, shaping how decisions are made and resources are allocated within the ecosystem. This topic is crucial for KBC because it ensures that power is distributed among participants rather than concentrated in the hands of a few. By enabling community members to have a say in the direction of the project, decentralized governance models foster transparency, inclusivity, and trust.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>