<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>KBC on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</title><link>https://borhez.com/tags/kbc/</link><description>Recent content in KBC on KBC by Master BoRHeZ</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.146.0</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borhez.com/tags/kbc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The role of ipv6 in the knowledgechain</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-04-the-role-of-ipv6-in-the-knowledgechain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-04-the-role-of-ipv6-in-the-knowledgechain/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Role of IPv6 in the KnowledgeChain&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, the importance of secure and efficient data transmission cannot be overstated. With the rise of blockchain technology, new opportunities have emerged to revolutionize the way we store and transfer information. One such project that is leading the charge in this space is Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the core of the KBC project lies the concept of verifiable knowledge, which aims to create a decentralized platform where users can securely share and access information. This is made possible through the use of Proof-of-Knowledge, a consensus mechanism that ensures the validity of data on the network. By leveraging the power of blockchain technology, KBC is able to establish trust and transparency in an otherwise opaque digital landscape.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Why kbc matters for science and innovation</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-04-why-kbc-matters-for-science-and-innovati/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-04-why-kbc-matters-for-science-and-innovati/</guid><description>&lt;p>Unlocking the Potential of Science and Innovation with Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, where information is constantly changing and evolving, the need for a reliable and secure system to verify knowledge has never been greater. This is where Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) comes into play, offering a revolutionary way to incentivize the creation and sharing of verifiable knowledge. KBC has the potential to transform the way we approach science and innovation, opening up new possibilities for collaboration and discovery.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Education and learning incentives in the lightweb</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-03-education-and-learning-incentives-in-the/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-03-education-and-learning-incentives-in-the/</guid><description>&lt;p>Education and Learning Incentives in the LightWeb&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, the value of education and continuous learning cannot be overstated. With the emergence of new technologies and innovations, staying ahead of the curve requires a commitment to expanding one&amp;rsquo;s knowledge base. The Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project aims to revolutionize the way we approach education and incentivize learning in the digital age.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Verifiable Knowledge: The Foundation of KBC&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the core of the KBC project is the concept of verifiable knowledge. In a world where misinformation and fake news run rampant, being able to verify the authenticity and accuracy of information is crucial. KBC leverages blockchain technology to ensure that knowledge is legitimate and trustworthy, empowering users to make informed decisions based on reliable sources.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The philosophy behind knowledge‑based currency</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-03-the-philosophy-behind-knowledge-based-cu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-03-the-philosophy-behind-knowledge-based-cu/</guid><description>&lt;p>Unlocking the Power of Knowledge: The Philosophy Behind Knowledge-Based Currency&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In a world where information is constantly flowing and evolving, the concept of Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) emerges as a beacon of innovation and empowerment. At its core, KBC is founded on the belief that knowledge is the most valuable asset we possess, and by leveraging this knowledge, we can create a more equitable and sustainable economy. In this blog post, we will delve into the philosophy behind KBC and explore the key ideas that drive this groundbreaking project.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How the k‑chain ensures trust and immutability</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-02-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immuta/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-02-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immuta/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ensuring Trust and Immutability with the K-Chain&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital world, trust and immutability are crucial factors when it comes to any kind of transaction or exchange of information. With the rise of blockchain technology, we have seen how decentralized systems can provide a level of security and transparency that was previously unimaginable. The Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project takes this concept to the next level with its innovative approach to verifiable knowledge and Proof-of-Knowledge.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The vision of lightweb as a decentralized knowledge internet</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-02-the-vision-of-lightweb-as-a-decentralize/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-08-02-the-vision-of-lightweb-as-a-decentralize/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Vision of LightWeb: A Decentralized Knowledge Internet&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the ever-evolving landscape of the digital age, the concept of a decentralized knowledge internet is becoming increasingly relevant. The Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project is at the forefront of this movement, with its innovative vision of LightWeb. This vision represents a paradigm shift in how we access and verify information online, offering a decentralized platform that empowers users to engage with knowledge in a new, secure, and transparent way.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How the k-chain ensures trust and immutability</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-07-31-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immutability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/2025-07-31-how-the-k-chain-ensures-trust-and-immutability/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="building-trust-in-knowledge-based-currency-the-role-of-k-chain">Building Trust in Knowledge-Based Currency: The Role of K-Chain&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>In an era where information is abundant yet often unreliable, the Knowledge-Based Currency (KBC) project emerges as a beacon of trust and innovation. At its core, KBC is designed to revolutionize how we perceive and utilize knowledge in digital transactions. A pivotal component of this groundbreaking system is the K-Chain, a technology that ensures trust and immutability. Let’s delve into how K-Chain, along with other components like Proof-of-Knowledge, LightWeb, and Oracle AI, transforms the landscape of digital currency.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is KBC?</title><link>https://borhez.com/posts/what-is-kbc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://borhez.com/posts/what-is-kbc/</guid><description>&lt;p>KBC stands for &lt;strong>Knowledge‑Based Currency&lt;/strong>, a novel form of money backed not by gold or government fiat but by verified knowledge. When you contribute a fact, a discovery or a solution to the KnowledgeChain, Oracle AIs validate it through a Proof of Knowledge process. If accepted, your contribution is recorded as a new block and you earn KBC tokens proportionate to its significance.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>KBC operates within an ecosystem that includes:&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>